tundra.com 2007-10-17

# Tundra Legal Notices & Privacy Policy

### "As Is" Disclaimer

The information on, or references from, this Web site are believed to be accurate and reliable. However, no responsibility is assumed by Tundra for its use. Tundra reserves the right to make changes to product specifications and documentation at any time without notice.

### Copyright Notice

This Web site and its contents are protected by copyright.

Copyright © 2007 Tundra Semiconductor Corporation. All rights reserved.  
Information contained on this Web site is subject to change without notice.

Except as specifically permitted herein, no portion of the information on this Web site may be reproduced in any form or in any manner without prior written permission by Tundra Semiconductor Corporation.

### Tundra Trademarks

Tundra trademarks represent valuable assets to the Company, and are protected against unauthorized use to the full extent afforded under international intellectual property laws.

TUNDRA and the Tundra logo are registered marks of Tundra Semiconductor Corporation in Canada, the European Union and the People's Republic of China (Registration is pending in the United States). 

Tsi106, Tsi107, Tsi108, Tsi109, Tsi110, Tsi205, Tsi206, Tsi248, Tsi252, Tsi257, Tsi301, Tsi308, Tsi310, Tsi340, Tsi350, Tsi352, Tsi381, Tsi384, Tsi400, Tsi500, Tsi564A, Tsi568A, Tsi574, Tsi576, Tsi578, Tsi148, Universe II, PowerSpan II, PowerSpan, QSpan II, QSpan, SCV64, DESIGN.CONNECT.GO, RIOLAB, the RIOLAB logo, SLE, the SLE logo and Think Physical are trademarks of Tundra Semiconductor Corporation.

All rights are reserved except for the logos, trademarks and copyrighted text of other companies. Product names, company names and logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective holders. Copyrighted text belonging to others is so marked.

**Comments/Questions**

We welcome any comments or questions with respect to Tundra's trademarks or copyright. Any comments or questions should be emailed to [webmaster@tundra.com](mailto:webmaster@tundra.com).  

### Tundra Website Privacy Policy

Tundra is committed to preserving your trust and confidence. That is why we want you to understand how we handle information we learn about you from your visit to this web site, what measures we take to safeguard that information and our commitment to data security. Because your privacy is important to us, Tundra will not sell, rent or trade your personal information collected on this site except as outlined in this Privacy Policy.

Tundra will not disclose your personal information without your express consent unless required to do so by law or unless Tundra has a good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (1) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process served on Tundra or this web site; (2) protect and defend the rights or property of Tundra and this web site; or (3) enforce its agreements with you. Tundra’s agreement not to disclose is subject to the following exceptions:

**Collection and Use of Data**

Tundra uses a commercial software package to analyze traffic to this web site. This information is used in aggregate to analyze and improve this web site.

We also may ask you for information that personally identifies you, such as your name, phone number, e-mail address, credit card number, and mailing address. Such personal information is collected only as part of an explicit registration process, such as that used in connection with purchasing or registering products, requesting additional information, participating in contests or surveys, receiving trial downloads, or registering for one of our training courses or events. This information allows us to process and fulfill your order, to register your subscriptions, to inform you of new products, services or offers, and to contact you if we need to obtain or provide additional information. We also use some personally identifiable information in conjunction with cookies and web behavioral data in order to help us better understand individual customer needs and behavior, as well as to tailor web site content and marketing messages to your interests.

**Disclosure of Data**

You agree that we may provide your information to our affiliates, resellers and business partners so that they may contact you for promotional purposes relating to Tundra products. As well, we may provide your information to third party service providers, such as fulfillment centers, mailing houses, event providers and customer support organizations. We will only provide those companies the information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose. Your information also may be transferred in connection with a sale, merger, transfer, exchange or other disposition (whether of assets, stock or otherwise) of all or a portion of a business of Tundra and/or its subsidiaries. While Tundra takes steps to protect the confidentiality, privacy and security of personal information communicated to these third parties, their activities are not subject to the exclusive control of Tundra and they are not subject to this privacy statement. As such, Tundra does not assume any liability for any damages or loss caused by these third parties’ activities.

**Updating and Removal of Data**

You may have your name removed from our direct and e-mail marketing lists at any time, by visiting our Update Account Information  page, and deselecting all check boxes. Alternatively, simply email us [webmaster@tundra.com](mailto:webmaster@tundra.com)  with your request.

**Security of Your Personal Information**

We have implemented industry standard security mechanisms and procedures to protect data from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.

**Children's Information**

Tundra.com is not a site that publishes content that is targeted to children, and we do not knowingly collect, use or disclose personally identifiable data on children under the age of 13.

**Use of Cookies**

Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. They allow us to better analyze our site traffic patterns and to provide improved content, advertisements, products and services. They also allow us to refine and enhance the visitor registration process and to add personalization. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that if you would rather not store the information for future use. If you disable the operation of cookies, you will be unable to access certain functionality on this web site and will not be able to purchase products directly through the web site.

**Your Consent**

By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information as outlined in this privacy policy. We may change our privacy policy at any time and without notice. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**Comments/Questions**

We welcome any comments or questions with respect to the Tundra Privacy Policy. Any comments or questions should be emailed to [webmaster@tundra.com](mailto:webmaster@tundra.com).
